locusmag.com 2004-06-10

# Locus Online: Privacy Policy

|    |  |  | 

**Locus Online** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices of [Locus Online](http://www.locusmag.com/). 

**Information Automatically Logged**

Each time a visitor comes to the **Locus Online** website, our host servers, like most on the web, collect some basic technical information, including the visitor's domain name. This data is compiled automatically but is not analyzed or shared with others. 

**Personal Information**

This website does not request any personal information or collect any information, either directly or by using cookies, that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted. Since we do not collect any personal information on this website, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes. 

Information provided when you subscribe to _Locus_ Magazine or order other material from _Locus_ (whether via this website's [Subscription/Order Form](https://amber.site-secure.net/locusmag/About/Subscribe.html), by phone, by fax, or by mail), such as credit card information and e-mail addresses, is not compiled by us or shared with others. Our website uses a secure server for pages that request credit card information -- the [Subscription/Order form](https://amber.site-secure.net/locusmag/About/Subscribe.html) and the [CD ROM Index ordering form](https://amber.site-secure.net/locusmag/About/CDRomAd.html). 

_Locus_ Magazine does share its subscription mailing list with others. You may request, when you subscribe, to be removed from this list. 

**Advertisers**

We have banner ads served onto our site by Advertising.com. These ads may contain cookies. Cookies received with banner ads are collected by Advertising.com, and **Locus Online** does not have access to this information. To visit Advertising.com's privacy statement, please click here <http://www.advertising.com/privacy/index.html>

**External Links**

This site contains links to other sites. **Locus Online** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. 

**Affiliate Relationships**

**Locus Online** is an associate of [Amazon.com Books](http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/redirect-home/locusmagazineA) and a branch of [Amazon.co.uk](http://www.amazon.co.uk/exec/obidos/redirect-home/1898). **Locus Online** earns a commission on products purchased from these websites by customers who link to them from our website. These websites may use cookies to identify you or track your order, but **Locus Online** does not have access to this information. Amazon.com and Amazon.co.uk provide us with reports of products browsed, and purchased, by visitors linking from **Locus Online** , but products are not identified by customer, and the information in these reports is not shared with others. 

**Letters to the Editor**

Letters sent to **Locus Online** , when posted, will include the writer's return e-mail address unless the writer requests us not to. Contact information, including e-mail addresses, is not compiled or shared with others. 

**Contacting the Website**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, contact [online@locusmag.com](mailto:online@locusmag.com).
